timevalue.com 2017-06-17

# Privacy Statement | TimeValue Software

TimeValue Software is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the [www.TimeValue.com](http://www.timevalue.com/) website and governs data collection and usage. By using the [www.TimeValue.com](http://www.timevalue.com/) website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

TimeValue Software collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. TimeValue Software also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by TimeValue Software. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by TimeValue Software for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the TimeValue Software website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through TimeValue Software public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: TimeValue Software does not read any of your private online communications.

TimeValue Software encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from TimeValue Software so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. TimeValue Software is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of TimeValue Software and the TimeValue Software family of websites.

**Use of your Personal Information**

TimeValue Software collects and uses your personal information to operate the TimeValue Software website and deliver the services you have requested. TimeValue Software also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from TimeValue Software and its affiliates; people may be added to a list and remarketed to. TimeValue Software may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

TimeValue Software does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. TimeValue Software may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, TimeValue Software may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to TimeValue Software, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

TimeValue Software does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

TimeValue Software keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within TimeValue Software, in order to determine what TimeValue Software services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within TimeValue Software to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

TimeValue Software websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TimeValue Software or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TimeValue Software; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of [www.TimeValue.com](http://www.timevalue.com/), or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The TimeValue Software website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize TimeValue Software’s pages, or register with TimeValue Software’s site or services, a cookie helps TimeValue Software to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same TimeValue Software website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the TimeValue Software features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the TimeValue Software services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

TimeValue Software secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. TimeValue Software secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Opt-out of Future Communication**

If you wish to unsubscribe from all future TimeValue Software e-mails, communications and offers, please send an email to [info@TimeValue.com](mailto:info@TimeValue.com?subject=Privacy%20Statement-Unsubscribe%20from%20emails). Be sure to request in the subject line "Please add me to TimeValue Software’s Do Not Contact List" and include your name and email address in the body of the email. A representative of TimeValue Software may subsequently contact you (via email) in order to obtain your feedback on the quality of the support you received. If you do not wish to participate, simply delete the survey email.

**Changes to this Statement**

TimeValue Software will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. TimeValue Software encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how TimeValue Software is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

TimeValue Software welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that TimeValue Software has not adhered to this Statement, please contact TimeValue Software at [info@TimeValue.com](mailto:info@TimeValue.com?subject=Statement%20of%20Privacy%20comments). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
